acquisio.com 2015-12-25

# Privacy Policy | Acquisio

The privacy of your personal information is very important. In order to provide you with our services, we use your personal info in a number of ways. This privacy policy outlines what personal information Acquisio collects about you and how we use it to operate the Acquisio service and any of our related Web-based services—we’ll refer to them as the “Service” just to make things clear here.

If you have any questions or concerns relating to privacy or security, please send an email to [yourprivacy@acquisio.com](mailto:yourprivacy@acquisio.com)

## What Information We Collect

To use Acquisio’s Service, you must provide personal info in order to create and activate an account. By “personal information,” we mean data that is unique to you as an individual—things like your name, address, e-mail address, company information (like your website address, average monthly paid search spend, average website traffic), telephone number, and credit card related information, and the username and password for your search engine and publisher accounts or other services you wish to connect to Acquisio. We will not collect additional personal information about you unless you provide us that information yourself.

## How We Use Your Information

Acquisio uses your personal information to contact you with questions about your account, to inform you about new features or offerings from Acquisio, to send you reminders, and to ask you for your feedback on how we can improve our Services. However, We do not sell your personal information or share it with third parties for marketing purposes. That said, we do need to share your personal information with Acquisio partners and service providers (e.g. Google AdWords, Microsoft adCenter, The Trade Desk, etc.) so that our Service works as it should. We also share financial and billing information with third parties solely to evaluate your credit status, to bill you for the Service, and for other administrative purposes. Beyond these uses, because we consider any personal information confidential, Acquisio will not disclose to third parties any identifying personal information gathered from you unless (a) you give us permission to share your personal information, or (b) we are required to disclose such information by any applicable law or legal process (like a subpoena or court order).

### Security

Acquisio utilizes generally-accepted security measures (such as encryption) to protect against the misuse or unauthorized disclosure of any personal information you submit to us. However, like other Internet sites, we cannot guarantee that it is completely secure against attempts to evade security measures or intercept transmissions over the Internet. You are responsible for maintaining the security of your username and password for the Service.

### Receiving Communications from Acquisio

If you no longer wish to receive marketing communications from Acquisio, simply click on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any marketing email sent to you by Acquisio. Please note that this does not apply to emails from Acquisio relating to billing, your account, or your normal use of the Service.

## Cookies

Cookies are pieces of data stored on your computer’s hard drive by a Web site. Cookies are an industry standard and used by most major Web sites to improve their services. Acquisio uses cookies to improve your experience. The cookie will tell our system certain information so you don’t have to fill in the same information each time you visit us. The Service can only read the cookies placed on your computer by us. We cannot access any information on your hard drive placed there by you or any other source. Please note that Acquisio uses third parties to assist us in measuring statistical information about users of the Service. Such parties may utilize cookies, but in no event will they connect any individual user with personally identifiable information or share any such information with anyone else. Also, the cookie feature can be turned off on your browser. For more information on turning off the cookie feature, consult your browser “Help” section. If you choose to turn off cookies, you can still access the Service, but you may not be able to utilize all of its features. In addition, you might have to “refuse” a cookie each time you encounter one searching the Service.

## IP Addresses

An Internet Protocol (IP) address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you access the Internet. This number may be the same each time you access the Internet or it may change. Like other Internet sites, Acquisio uses IP addresses to collect aggregate information about numbers of visitors and site usage. Acquisio reserves the right to use IP addresses to identify individuals if (1) Acquisio is required to disclose such information by any applicable law or legal process (like a subpoena or court order); or (2) Acquisio is required to do so to protect the safety of the public or other users of the Service, to enforce the Terms of Use, or otherwise to protect our rights.

## Surveys and Polls

If you respond to any surveys or polls on our site, we may ask you for demographic information such as your location, ecommerce data, gender or age. This information is collected only as anonymous, aggregated information and is used for statistical purposes.

## Children

The Service is intended for marketers and agencies and is not targeted to people under the age of 18. If you become aware that a child has used the Service and/or provided personal information, please contact Acquisio immediately at [yourprivacy@acquisio.com](mailto:yourprivacy@acquisio.com). If we become aware that a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information, we will promptly remove such information from our servers.

## Other Web Sites and Content

This privacy policy applies only as long as you remain on the Service. The Service may contain links to third-party sites or services, and once you leave the Service to visit another site, we have no control over your privacy or security issues even if you reached the other site by clicking on a link within the Service. We recommend you familiarize yourself with the policies of these other sites and services. Acquisio assumes no responsibility or liability for the availability or content of these outside sites, including any products, services or materials which may be available from such sites. Therefore, any concerns a user may have regarding any other site should be directed to the relevant site administrator or webmaster.

## Changes to this Policy

If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our website to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. You are bound by changes to the Privacy Policy when you use the site and/or our Service after those changes have been posted.
